FATIK OWAIS

UI/UX Engineer



CONTACT

+92-333-3368701 fatikowais@gmail.com

EDUCATION

2011-2015 **NED University -** Bachelors in Computer & Information
Systems Engineering

2009-2011 **D.J Science College**

1999-2009 **Al-Saqib Public School**

PROFILE

An artist who uses his technical knowledge to come up with creative solutions to the challanges.

With the mission of creating delight|ful experiences for the end user I have a knack for attention to details who plays a crucial role in the every step of product development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX DESIGNER . TEKVARE. 2018-PRESENT

Producing UI of webistes including its imagery and animation

FRONT END DEVELOPER. ARPATECH. 2017-2018

Built an API for e-commerce website that lets user visualize their custom design in a realistic 3d representation.

BRAND EXECUTIVE. ARPATECH. 2017

Managed and worked alongside marketing team to design products and to keep their brand identity consistent.

CREATIVE MANAGER. HAYTHAMS. 2016

Managed and worked with a team of graphic designers, animators, and videographers.

SKILLS & TOOLS

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

Iconography, illustration, logo, vectorization, scene design

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

Website visualization, UI components design, photo retouch & editing, animated GIFs

ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS

2d animation videos, UI animation, motion graphics

SKETCH 3

Responsive prototypes, mobile apps UI/UX, customer journey design & rapid prototyping

WEB APP DEVELOPMENT

HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS(beginner level), Bootstrap, Foundation,